# artikasbe16@ymail.com 8369735220

Mumbai, India 400070

## Skills

- Smooth operations management
- · Process improvement
- · Business operations
- CRM
- Customer service and satisfaction
- Vendor management
- Client interaction
- · Team management
- Quality management
- Time management
- Budgeting & Negotiation
- · MIS reporting

## Education

2013

MMS:

Finance

**Mumbai University** 

CGPA: 5.02

2012

B. COM:

**Siddharth College** 

Mumbai

67 %

2009

HSC:

**Siddharth College** 

Mumbai

52 %

2007

SSC:

**MMGS School** 

Mumbai

52%

# ARTI KASHINATH KASBE

# Summary

Operations Manager with 10 years of experience coordinating operations to achieve organizational goals, implementing new processes and managing and planning innovations. Bringing outstanding problem-solving and abilities paired with in-depth knowledge of policies and procedures. Polished in evaluating employee performance and overseeing key projects.

## Experience

#### **HDFC Credila Financial Services Limited - Operations Manager**

04/2023 - Current

- Ensure transactions details are accurate and give authorization accordingly
- Ensure banking activities are completed in a timely manner to avoid any escalations
- Ensure proper handling of loan and customer property documents with updated trackers for reference
- Ensure all KYC and loan related documents are received by each and every customer
- Adhering timelines and handling of sales, operations team and all concerned parties
- Prepare and initiate financial reports, progressive reports such as Verifications
- Good attitude towards Intra department coordination and handling third party vendors
- Working on end-to-end file login and disbursement and working on fulfilment of customer journey with the institution
- Ensure compliance in identification and scanning of documents
- Managing filing, documentation and working on education loan as per requirement
- Open to work with new projects and activities pertaining to day-to-day operations activities.

#### **EBSC Technologies Private Limited - Senior Operations Manager**

Mumbai

08/2022 - 04/2023

- Develop strategies to grow the CRM database
- Create and implement the plans for rolling out the strategy in close collaboration with Business Unit
- Closely cooperate with BU and Sales to implement CRM activities as according to the CRM calendar
- Responsible for ensuring system and processes are complaint and the integrity of patient data is maintained
- Leads large, geographically distributed, cross-line-of-business teams
- Support the Sales organization with CRM needs, understand business requirements and translate them into detailed technical requirements, roll out

## Certifications & Awards

- Certified Operational Excellence Internal Auditor & Documentation Rewarded through STM (Start of the Month)
- Certified TTT (Train the Trainer)
- · Desk Top Publishing
- Microsoft Office Specialist (Excel, Word & Power Point)

# Languages

English:	B2
Upper Intermediate	
Hindi:	C2
Proficient	
Marathi:	C2
Proficient	

- new products and features
- User account creation in CRM (Leadsquared, Ameyo, etc.)
- Vendor Coordination for billing, payment, product level changes and new feature add on
- Customers and source coordination for business growth
- Business partner onboarding process
- Customers pre and post sales services
- Ensure team trained on the process
- Business MIS and analysis
- Data maintenance and performance analysis

## Whitehat Education Technology Pvt. Ltd - Assistant Manager - Operations

Powai, Mumbai

09/2021 - 08/2022

- Ensure proper Workflow Management and adherence to timeline as per the process defined
- Engage with Teachers and Students on the platform to schedule the classes
- Ensure that the content management system is updated at all times
- Ensure that all associated content like Class Summaries, Graphics, etc are in place
- Ensure Audits and new lesson plans and projects created
- Analyze Curriculum Metrics on a weekly basis (Class Consumption, Project Submission, Class Duration
- Inactive Students, Trial Conversion, Renewal%, etc.)
- Get user feedbacks for all classes which have quality or duration breach and share insights
- Solve Curriculum Escalations from Customers (Students/Parents and Teachers)
- Ensure Curriculum Improvements are done by liaising with the Curriculum Subject Matter Experts

#### **Edubridge Learning Pvt. Ltd - Operations Manager**

Santacruz, Mumbai 08/2019 - 10/2020

- Monitor & review daily performance, assigned inventory management, data upload, process adherence
- Improvements, operations evaluation.
- Drive process excellence & business operation development
- Support & help regional operation to perform as per guideline set in SOPs & CPS (Critical Path to Success)
- Identify improvement opportunities for process excellence
- Monitor & evaluate regional operation performances monthly
- Ensure correct data upload on Govt Portal
- Ensure financial closing (Invoices) on time with finance team
- Groom operation team for innovation, problem solving, proactive approach, customer focus, process excellence, team work, time management.
- Work independently in the emergency situation
- Monitor, review, evaluate MIS reporting from operation.
- Review call with top management, regional operations & HR.

#### Regime Tax Solutions Pvt. Ltd - Operations Team Leader

Vashi, Mumbai 09/2018 - 08/2019

- Coordinated, developed and scheduling deliverables to clients meeting time critical deadlines.
- Managed new clients for their operational requirements, services, queries etc.
- Monitored & evaluate customer complaints, queries in professional manner.
- Updated, tracked and monitored operations performance, executed monthly reports and projections
- Communicated daily with staffs ensuring that tax service runs problem-free and on schedule.
- Updated departmental standard operating procedures and database to accurately reflect the current.
- Identified inefficiencies and implemented process improvements in areas such as security, quality, and excellent operation.
- Conducted daily and weekly piece counts on team members.

#### **NSEIT Ltd - Operations Team Leader**

Andheri, Mumbai 09/2015 - 08/2018

- Play a significant role in long-term planning, including an initiative geared toward operational excellence.
- Track the progress of weekly, monthly, quarterly and annual objectives
- Also Evaluate employee performance and identify hiring and training needs.
- Monitored and managed operational activities
- Directed the functions/Centre/venues operational risks, financial aspects and QA and audit processes.
- Coordinate Internal compliance and third-party audit for ISO 9001(QMS) & ISO 20000 (ITSM).
- Designed and coordinated training programs for employees in order to enhance work efficiency – Conducted training sessions and workshops to improve the workforce and productivity of the firm.
- Prepare, review process flow charts & process activity documents as per ISO & Organization requirements.
- Create reports, dashboard, analyze and interpret real data, like revenues, expenses and competition.

## **Kevat Enterprises - Back Office Executive**

Mumbai 05/2012 - 09/2015

- Reverts of E-mails
- Customers Queries
- Data uploading in Excel
- Courier follow-up for tracking